They're not just employees at
that company, they're like, OMG,
their salaries are ridiculous.  So again that alone
we have an idea and that would lead to
that that can be lead to what to
individual seats for that matter no.  So
here is our requirement
from five to 10 initially enrolled
members and then the premium requirement
would increase from Php2,000 to
Php10,000.
And here, the riders,
we need to tweak it a bit
depending on the requirements of the
client.  But still standard is accident
in the TPT.  That's still standard
.  But we have the C, the critical
illness rider.
We have HIV and AMR.  So
he is the same.  But
really, this is just for
men in companies.  And that's what
you said earlier, your asel, when it
exceeds 20%, they can no longer be
in the group protection.  They're here,
they're here automatically when there are too
many of them, what is the composition of
substandard occupations?
Yes.
Are they contractors?  They can't be
here either.  Yes.  What is
definitely
so FI only? We almost don't have any
companies that are denied under ESP.
We also reject almost no
occupation.  I know of only one
occupation that we reject or
don't cover.  Do you know
Spiderman?
Yes.  They are the ones who clean the
buildings.  As far as I know, that's the only
occupation Manul is pursuing right now, Spiderman.
All the rest.  So construction workers,
security guards can be stolen.  Yes sir, legit
requires a legit entity.
Legitimate entity.  Yes.  Okay, okay,
that's great, for now, let's not venture
or partner
with those particular groups. The question
he asked is about uniformed arms and personnel,
meaning soldiers and their
dependencies. So if we have an account on
that, let's not do it for groups,
but for individuals. There's no one stopping, no one stopping,
kagawad, kagawad, kagawad, kagawad.
Yes.  For
approval, as long as our ESP is for
approval, yes, we do cover the agent.
Okay.
Yes.
Ah, it's possible that the LGU's budget
will pay for the entire council,
that's also possible.  It's also possible.
But it's a bit of
So but yes we can.
Any questions?  Considering the number,
the information is less.  Sorry,
the information is less because there are
many Yeses.  Are you right there?  Yes.  Because
we are assessing them as a group based
on their occupation, based on the
industry that they are falling into.  No,
so that's what a group is, right?  But that's what
you get for individual
information that will translate to
individual groups, that is, individual sales.   The
minimum number of this is 10, sir,
10 customizations, 10 minis.
The occupations are substandard, not by
value. The
minimum is 10, not by value.  No,
earlier yes, earlier value.  You're right about
this one, whatever
they requested, as long as we meet the
10,000 premium attempt lives.
Let's say for ESP in particular
it is subject for underwriting.
Not necessarily sir
for ESP no but by rule when the
employee is less than 25 for ESP ha if
less than 25 subject to underwriting by
rule when less than 25. So when
we exceed 25 ah 100,000 there is no noted
evidence limit.  That means
automatic coverage without submitting
any form of insurability no and also by
rule when it's small of course we cannot
cover them for 1 million if there are only 10 of
them requesting 1 million sorry we
cannot do that because one person will just die loss loss loss loss
no it's not just
loss loss loss loss loss man life
because it's very cheap magividual
mag-individual na lang tama yun true
yun miss because we have accounts
we we really cannot offer their desired
protection under group.  So what
they do is they individualize.
They are individual.
Okay.
Sir, we're clear here, right?  So I said
for this particular session,
maybe we can come back again for
another on the other products like the
group credit line.  This is it.  So I'll just go back
.  Yes, sir.  Let's go.  So but
this is to be customized.  So that
means let's say rock and fight,
it's up to the company.  Yes, sir.
Hey executives, what kind of coverage is there, is
there a maximum, is there not?  Um currently at 50
million but so far no one is taking
50 million.  So you saw it earlier,
sorry
you didn't see it in the letter.  So I think we
could apply that insurance
where the executives sometimes the
top brushes in a company are actually
bought by the owner of the insurance because
these should be his work when
one of the top key people dies because the top
key person in the in
' will disappear the operation can be lined up
' isn't it to be replaced immediately that's what
a company does
he needs to get a
replacement
normally to get that they buy
people from other companies so that's what
will be used sometimes pro okay so that is
effect on insurance okay so that's
one of the effects insurance but at the
same time insurance will also retain
that particular person loyal to the
company because those benefits there those
beneficial ones there can also be for the
the family of the of
Yes.  So um actually just to excite you
even more no so by next year there are
plans.  We cannot just commit on
when it will be launched no but going
back for us to be in a one stop shop no
so when we engage a corporate
account by next year we will all be over there may
be UITF the corps and
the MEMTC will also take time on how this will be translated
and then automatically we will be
offering um critical illness automatically
no once an engagement
immediately critical illness and I mean
we said we will just find all the ways to
sell so that's the same thing what
the management and the corps want because
they said they saw Rahul no they
management it's really a waste the
opportunity is there there is there no so
I mean let's use that
opportunity that's the door opener
so we will offer everything yes p what will happen
PC he said.  What is a PC?
He'll start counting.  He was actually counted
among the BPC.  Yes.
So this is actually what he counted on
.  So I'll just highlight
one particular product right now because
we'll talk about that one at length.  Standard
commission of 12%.  It's standard
for package products, 12% if customized
can be lowered because sometimes
you really have to sacrifice to get the
account.  And then ORC rates on the first
year.  This is our production credit
.  So yes, he counts for all of
your promos,
whatever.  Whatever we have
in the agency, as long as it's PC-based,
it's counted, right?  Of course, only one case count
.  That's the only case count for the
group.
So we can have many
case counts from the employees.
An employee who
immediately receives many awards is a lucky
winner.   That's right,
because the benefits are
locked up in people.  Yes,
Miss Joy is right.
Yes.  It's good, or is Miss Joy's memory of it again? It's
just one case, but that's
the whole thing that penetrates the employees.
That's what I'm saying, I'll
be very honest. I cannot guarantee that
you will win all the accounts that
we operate with corporate
products.  Right?  I can't.
We will lose, we will win.  But what
we definitely have no defeat in is the ability to
penetrate.  Okay?  That's the one who is
invincible.  And unfortunately,
what I see wrong is that the
common pitfall is losing.
Of course not, it's already lost, right?  I don't want to
use the relationship anymore.
That's it or sometimes it won or it was already
in the PC and
commission there in the group suddenly stopped
not realizing that it's a pity very chamy
chamininess we were in HR oh
I can be a magano here financial
wellness so again po again the objective
of this discussion is yes to reinforce
that everything is counted that in any in
any entity whether big or small
entity that you engage with no for
corporate products one thing remains
true and certain you get information of
the employees that can help you make or
generate the the what the individual
proposal
let's create a more beautiful
relationship with the HR so that
we can sell inside there are many
magang ganong successful stories um I
think if you have attended One of Jo
Casare do you know Jo Casareo?
Because he's one of those guys who
uses his body and
product a lot even when he loses.  Sometimes
even if he loses, it's okay.
Miss Julie keeps telling me it's
okay.  I mean, it's okay of course
she is bad.  She lost but
she was a winner in the individual because
she really didn't use the
relationship even though she lost or even though
she wasn't entertained sometimes in HR
it happens but it didn't stop her from
what is she using the
successful story of Josh and the girly in
worksite marketing because really in any
in all in all of our corporate
engagement
lost win she asked to do
nesting and then financial wellness
the financial wellness you've got a
very good said sir you got a very
good material
but we can also help
our work setting it needs to be it needs to be no so
that's what we don't forget
no yes madam you want to say something
maam there are many because
how about if we bring the work together
then be able to share
yeah we can do we can do splitting
up to you up to you up to you that's a
good question that's tru that's
true
in one account multiple agents can
so far we have experience at the most three
three not what say multiple two
or three can sir can can three can
make it to 100 employees.  Ah sir, in the
group, what will happen is one particular
account 30 33,
so your commission,
your PC, even the case is okay,
the percentage is up to you
.  It shouldn't be 3030
pictures that are
1% but it's possible or it's possible, no,
I'm live, we can do this by the way, no of
course not confident to present, we can present
for you, wow, proposal,
what an initial approach,
you just gathered data, we have a proposal,
we can do the presentation,
our team.  Yes.  Just let us know
ahead of time.  No.  So when we say um
allow us to help you in presenting or
explaining the benefits of our proposal
but do the initial approach meetings
once the
yes is still young if 3,000 man power.   It's
not true, it's true, what's the
100? Okay, let's be specific about
this Metro Manila, there's no problem, relatively
nearby provinces like Bilak Bulacan,
there's no problem, we can easily do
that, but if we go far away, there's an airplane,
there's accommodation, minimum of Php
500,
premium, premium, premium,
premium,
yes, if you take us far away, like for
example, we have to fly to Ilocos or to
Mindanao.  Even I've gone to Mindanao one
time.  That's okay.  No
problem.  You can also zoom.  It's also possible.
Yes.  We do we can go face to face one
then hide.  It can also take
a few weeks for your
let's say out of town booking scheduling
flights airf what if ah if out
of the out of Metro Manila really like
those maybe 2 weeks 2 weeks
2 weeks but if in Metro Manila 3
weeks sorry 3 days before 3 to 5 days
when virtual honestly it's pretty easy to
adjust if virtual it's easy to
insert.  But if your requirement is face to face
, please let us
know about 5 days ahead.  What is
Manila's answer if it's only Metro Manila, Manul's answer is
outside.  Ah,
our answer is still the same, but that's why you have a ping premium
requirement.  Okay, so prem.  So to make it
very simple for everyone it's always
case to case basis depending on the account.
Then definitely if it's a big account,
time will be given.  It's that simple.
Okay?  Because you might still have a lot of questions
.  Okay, maybe the
essence of the presentation will be lost.  Okay.  As long as
it's really a good account that will
matter to the company, definitely you
will always be supported.  That's it.  There is a
question here in terms of if
he doesn't want to, he doesn't want to have a partner, can you also be
with him,
he said I don't want to have a partner, okay, okay,
he doesn't hate
him, but he owes money, no, that's right,
I'm free, free, free, with him, love
opening, love opening, I laugh, there are
guys, even our very own
top of our top, be ballete,
is that she's one of the top producers
of body life, in our no part, who is
part of her, she would always deal with you,
Julie, okay, that's what's always being
used today, as a hard door
opener, really, so imagine
Bente, you're just closing 100
million all the time, even small
companies, stores like this,
inside the parlor, penetrating that to
talk to the owner, okay, that's
his strategy, really, he's like that, okay, so it's a
huge opportunity,
yes, so to cut it short, let's be fair,
in a very layman's term, let's be fair,
even if it's small, let's not be judgmental, they don't have money, no, don't
be judgmental, they don't have
money, no, don't  that's all, so that's all
p so again thank you so much and
Um, I'll be sending I'll be sending all
the materials once we have received.
Ah, trade license tradition.   The
government is a party list, ask
the commission.  government yeah
education is pretty good
to be very
possible how about insurance
ah because we need to get certain approvals
because it's very specific because from where we
get approvals from it's not possible if that's how it should be, it should be just like this
who
they are actually reporting to that are
actually allowed to get the insurance
from
Sorry
sorry.  There are no minimum attendees,
no group attendees at the
meeting, even if it's just one person, it can
only be HR, the company or
company owner.
Ma'am, are there any requirements that
the company will send to us?
Yes, sir.  So that's a good question
.  I just forgot.
Just the franchise form and then the master list,
that's all.  That's all.  Side side
franchise form and master.  It's Dung Day
at the company, sir.  Ah, when
it's closed.  Oh okay.  Yes.  When it's already closed
.  Okay.  You cannot
make a proposal to them
without the franchise form.  Is that the
first step?  Okay?  They will not touch
that account without the franchise form.
Okay.  So where to find the
franchise form is
up to you.
I don't know which of
her
you want and which of her.
So, um, that's it.  So thank you so much
for a very engaging session no.  So let's not do
this, don't be
shy about asking. I understand and I
would really, you know, I wouldn't
take it against you if you forgot
even after this,
but I'm free. There's no
charge for any questions. No, there's no charge for
asking, so just ask.  So
I'll be sending all our contact
information when we send
all the materials to you guys.  So that's it
.  Thank you very much.  I'll be back
again by next year.  It's really like
our road show.  But at
least for this time, let's just focus on
our corporate accounts being a door
opener.  Thank you very much.
Thank you.